

JavaScript

Libraries:

React

jQuery

Version

Control:

• Git

• React Native

SKILLS

Technologies:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Node.js

Databases:

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

Software Development:

• Agile

PORTFOLIO



marcelo-peralta.vercel.app



github.com/marcelosperalta

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Mother Tongue

English: Fluent (C1)

German: Beginner (A1)

CONTACT ME AT

- Quitzowstraße 106, 10551, Berlin, Germany
- +49 0 178 130 0799
- marcelosperalta@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ in marcelosoaresperalta

MARCELO SOARES PERALTA

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

As a former System Administrator, I have a strong IT background, with 6+ years' experience in Data Center environment. Good understanding of ITIL best practices. Currently, I am studying Web Development at DCI Digital Career Institute Berlin to change my career and become a fullstack developer (MERN stack).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Media Moderator

Majorel, Berlin | Feb 2018 - Nov 2019

Moderate content using internal moderation policies.

Social Media Moderator

ARWA Personaldienstleistungen, Berlin | Jun 2017 - Feb 2018

• Moderate content using internal moderation policies.

System Administrator

Global Hitss, São Paulo, Brazil | Sep 2016 - Dec 2016

- Windows Server management.
- Server virtualization with VMware tools.
- Microsoft Active Directory management.

System Administrator

Stefanini, São Paulo, Brazil | Aug 2014 - Aug 2016

- Windows Server management.
- Server virtualization with VMware tools.
- Microsoft Active Directory management.

EDI Support

Stefanini, São Paulo, Brazil | Mar 2013 - Jul 2014

- EDI implementation and support.
- T-Systems rvsXP support.



JavaScript

Libraries:

React

jQuery

Version

Control:

• Git

• React Native

SKILLS

Technologies:

• HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Node.js

Databases:

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Software Development:

• Agile

PORTFOLIO

marcelo-peralta.vercel.app

github.com/marcelosperalta

LANGUAGES

Portuguese: Mother Tongue

English: Fluent (C1)

German: Beginner (A1)

CONTACT ME AT

- Quitzowstraße 106, 10551, Berlin, Germany
- +49 0 178 130 0799
- marcelosperalta@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ in marcelosoaresperalta

MARCELO SOARES PERALTA

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Team Leader

Stefanini, São Paulo, Brazil | Jul 2011 - Feb 2013

- Process and procedures revision and design.
- Reports creation and presentation.
- Responsible for ticket management and change process.

Data Center Operator

Stefanini, São Paulo, Brazil | Oct 2010 - Jun 2011

- Servers, network equipment, appliances and Internet/Intranet backbone monitoring via Nagios.
- Symantec BackupExec management.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Fullstack Web Development

DCI Digital Career Institute gGmBH, Berlin | Dec 2019 - Jan 2021

- Accomplishing a one-year full-time training.
- Creating multiple projects using HTML, CSS, Sass, JavaScript and MERN stack.

Technologist in Systems Analysis and Development Fatec Zona Sul, São Paulo, Brazil | Aug 2011 - Jun 2014

- Design and implement systems according to institutional needs.
- Coordinate information technology infrastructures, developing policies and guidelines based on the need analysis.
- Perform consultancy in Information Systems, evaluation, and choice of software and hardware resources.

Technician in Electrical and Electronics SENAI Ary Torres, São Paulo, Brazil | Feb 2006 - Nov 2007

• Through the study of electricity, analog and digital electronics, among other top, I was qualified to work on the development, installation and maintenance of low voltage electronic systems.